>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 希望你能对这项运动有相当的感觉
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So hopefully you
feel pretty good about that exercise,
希望是有道理的
hopefully it made sense.
让我们深入了解一下我们的定义是多填充。
Let's dive in and try our hand at
defining this object is polyfill.
第一个，记住，
So number one, remember,
我们需要一个 if 语句，以检查是否未定义 Object.is 。
we want an if statement that checks to
see that Object.is has not been defined.
现在我要用这个简短的速记
Now, I'm gonna go ahead and
use this little shorthand here,
这一布尔胁迫我就会说反对的是反对
this Boolean coercion, I'm gonna
say that the negate of Object.is.
因此，如果已经定义了 Object.is ，
So if Object.is has been defined,
它被定义的唯一方法就是发挥作用
the only way that it ever gets
defined is as a function.
所以它绝对是在你的名单上，如果我否定它，
So it's definitely on the truthy list,
and if I negate it, and
如果不在那里肯定是没有定义的
if it's not there,
it's definitely undefined.
所以对我来说，这就是我在布尔胁迫下可以接受的地方之一
So to me, this is one of those places
where I'm okay with the Boolean coercion
因为我们只检查未定义的和完全存在的情况
because, hey, we're only checking either
undefined versus totally present.
这里真的没有地方
There's really nowhere in between.
所以我们是说如果不是 Object.is，我会投这个
So we're saying if not Object.is, and
I'm gonna throw in this or true for
就在刚才我们确定我们正在运行我们的功能
just now, just so we make sure that
we're actually running our function.
我第一次做这个练习时犯了这个错误
The first time I made this exercise,
I made that mistake, and
我不知道为什么事情不工作了
I couldn't figure out why things
weren't working, [LAUGH] or
为什么在我破解密码的时候都还在工作呢
why things were still working
even when I had broken code.
所以，犯这些错误很容易。
So it's easy to make those mistakes.
好了我们要定义一个对象是函数
All right, so we're gonna define one,
Object.is = function, and
我叫它 Object.is，如果我能输入的话。
I'll just name it Object.is,
if I could ever type.
它需要两个参数，所以我将它叫做 x 和 y。
And it's gonna take two parameters,
so I'll call it x and y.
如果你觉得更好的话，你可以称之为 v1 和 v2 。
You could call it v1 and
v2 if you feel better about that.
同样地， Object.is 的工作本质上是三重平等，
Again, the job of Object.is is
essentially the triple equals,
但在负 0 和 NaN 的情况下也不需要撒谎。
but also it needs to not lie in
the cases of negative 0 and NaN.
所以这里有一点细微差别
So there's a little bit of nuance here,
我已经知道了所以我就跳过去
which I happened to already know about,
so I'll just jump to it.
我们想拿到一个指标如果你愿意的话
We wanna go ahead and get an indicator,
a true false if you will,
x 为负 0 ， y 是否为负 0。
of whether x is a negative 0 and
whether y is a negative 0.
所以我要叫它 xNegZero;
So I'm gonna call it
xNegZero; y negative zero,
这些都是我给你分配的变量
those are just gonna be variables
that I assign to here in a moment.
我要给他们分配的结果是
And what I'm gonna assign them is
the result of testing a value for
它的负面 zeroness
its negative zeroness.
所以我要给你一个小帮手
So I'm gonna define a little helper for
我自己想知道是否有负面影响
myself to figure out if
something is a negative 0.
我不知道你们中是否有任何一个人
I wonder if any of you were able to
come up with a way of doing that without
建在 object.is?
the built in object.is?
有人吗
Anyone?
> > 学生: 几周前我偶然无意中发现了它。
&gt;&gt; Student: I stumbled across it
a couple weeks ago accidentally.
> > Kyle Simpson: 好的，所以你-- > > Student : 所以我作弊了。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Okay, so you-
&gt;&gt; Student: So I cheated.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 你已经看到了，好，酷。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: You happened to
have already seen it, okay, cool.
那我们该怎么做呢
Well how would we do that?
这个有点棘手，所以如果你不明白，就别难过了。
This one's a little tricky, so
if you didn't get it, don't feel bad.
但如果你想想一个负 0的值
But if you think about
a value that is negative 0,
我们对 0 的操作有什么了解 ?
what do we know about operations
that we can do with 0?
所以如果你说，负 0 ，你给它加 0 吧 ?
So if you say, take a negative 0,
and you add a 0 to it?
如果你知道你只会得到一个普通的 0
Well, if you do that you know
you're just gonna get a regular 0.
如果你把 0 和 0 都减去 0 就没别的事了
If you take a negative 0 and you subtract
a 0 from it nothing else is gonna happen,
还会是 0 比 0
it's still gonna be a negative 0.
所以加减是不会有帮助的
So adding and
subtracting aren't gonna help.
但分组的情况如何呢 ?
But what about division?
我们知道，例如， 1 除以 0 给我们无穷大。
We know that for example,
1 divided by 0 gives us infinity.
你认为一个负 0 会给我们什么 ?
What do you think one 1 by
negative 0 would give us?
>> Student2: 负无穷大。
&gt;&gt; Student2: Negative infinity.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 负无穷大。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Negative infinity.
所以有一个测试方法如果我们有一个阴性的 0
So there's a way of testing
if we have a negative 0,
我们唯一能得到负无穷大的方法就是如果我们有一个负的 0
the only way we could get negative
infinity is if we had a negative 0.
也许不是唯一的办法但这就是我们要做的
Maybe not the only way but
that's the way we're gonna do it.
所以我想说如果 NegZero 值不高我会说首先
So I'm gonna say if NegZero take in
a value, and I'm gonna say, first of all,
我们得确保它是两个 0 中的一个因为如果它是无穷大的
we need to make sure it's one of
the two 0 because if it was infinity,
这会给我们一个错误的正面
that would give us a false positive here.
所以我们会说如果是两个 0s 中的一个
So we'll say, if v is one of the two 0s,
我们可以用双等号还是三等
which we can either use the double
equals or the triple equals.
在这种情况下，两者之间不会有任何区别。
In this case, they would not have
any distinction between the two.
所以如果是两个 0中的一个
So if it's one of the two 0,
然后我们就会说
and, and then we're gonna say
( 1/v) == -Infinity。
(1/v) == -Infinity.
这就是我们如何知道的 -- >> Student3:
That's how we could know-
&gt;&gt; Student3: Was that a constant in
JavaScript?
>> Kyle Simpson: Infinity 是内置的。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Infinity is a built-in.
>> Student3: 真的吗 ? >> 凯尔 - 辛普森:
&gt;&gt; Student3: Really?
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Yep,
它是一个内置的标识。
it's a built-in identifier.
>> Student3: 好的。
&gt;&gt; Student3: Okay.
>> Kyle Simpson: 因此，除以 v 会给我们负无穷大，如果和
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So 1 divided by v
would give us negative infinity, if and
仅当 v 为负 0时。
only if v was negative 0.
再一次，此检查的原因是 1 除以负无穷大，
Again, the reason for this check
is 1 divided by negative infinity,
也会带来无限的无限
would also give negative infinity.
所以，我们不想在这里有任何假阳性。
[LAUGH] So, we don't wanna
have any false positives here.
好了这就是我们要检查 X 和 Y 的情况
Okay, so that's how we're going to
check if x and y are negative 0s,
我们会叫那个小公用事业的
we're gonna call that little utility.
所以我们会说，如果 isItNegZero(x)
So we'll say, if isItNegZero(x), and
那我们就会说 isItNegZero(y)
then we'll say if isItNegZero(y).
现在我们想做的第一件事就是
Now, the first thing we
wanna do is if either x or
y 是负 0 我们会检查它们是否都是
y is a negative 0 then we're
gonna check if both of them are.
但我们得先检查我们是否在处理
But we need to first check if
we're dealing with the case that
其中之一为负 0。
either one of them is the negative 0.
因为如果其中一个是负 0
Because if either one
of them is negative 0,
我们知道三等同体会说谎所以我们不能让它发生
we know that the triple equals is gonna
lie, so we can't allow that to occur.
所以我们要说如果 (xNegZero 或 yNegZero )
So we're gonna say,
if (xNegZero or yNegZero),
那将会是我们的条件之一我们会处理这事的
that's gonna be one of our conditions,
and we'll handle what to do with that.
现在，如果不是这样的话，
Now, if that's not the case,
the next thing that
我们得检查 X 和 y 都是 NN
we need to check is if both the x and
the y are NaNs.
和我一起吗
Everybody with me?
如果两者都是 NN ，那么我们就想回归真实，
If both of them are NaNs,
then we wanna return true,
因为我们知道三等号等于是假的
because we know that's the case where
triple equals would return a false false,
如果你愿意的话就会撒谎说假话
if you will, it would lie and say false.
因此，我们需要另一个实用程序来检查 NN。
So we need another utility for
checking for NaNs.
您只能使用 number.isNaN ，但是
You could just use number.isNaN, but
README 建议请您尝试使用它。
the README suggested maybe try
your hand to coming up with it.
有没有人来测试过
Did anyone come up with a way
of testing for testing for
没有内置实用程序的 NaN ?
NaN without the built-in utilities?
几个星期前你也看到过那个 [ 洛杉矶 ] 吗
Did you also see that one
[LAUGH] a couple of weeks ago?
好吧你怎么想的
Okay, what did you come up with?
> > 学生: 有点 jenky。
&gt;&gt; Student: It's kinda jenky.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 这是什么 ? >> Student : 但是它是一个检查
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: What is it?
&gt;&gt; Student: But it's an if that checks if
param1 不等于 param1 或 param2 不等于 param2。
param1 is not equal to param1 or
param2 is not equal to param2.
>> 凯尔辛普森: 好的。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Okay.
>> Student: 然后在里面返回类型的 param1 是数字和
&gt;&gt; Student: And then inside there
returns type of param1 is number and
param2 的类型是数字，那么它们是唯一不等于的数字
type of param2 is number, then they're
the only numbers that are not equal
对他们自己 -- > 凯尔 - 辛普森: 好的。
to themselves-
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Okay.
>> Student: [CROSSTALK] NN。
&gt;&gt; Student: [CROSSTALK] NaNs.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 你在正确的轨道上。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: You're
on the right track.
我想我们甚至能做得更简单你就在正确的轨道上
I think we can even do this simpler,
you're on the right track.
这里的具体窍门是 NaN 是唯一值
The specific trick here is
that NaN is the only value in
在 JavaScript 中存在与自身不相等的情况。
existence in JavaScript
that's not equal to itself.
所以如果我传入 NaN ，它将不等于自身
So if I pass in a NaN,
it will be not equal to itself and
否则一切都将失败
everything else that would fail.
所以我们可以简单地说， v 不等于自己。
So we can simply say,
v not equal to itself.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 而 NaN 是唯一能从那里回归的人。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: And NaN is the only
one that would return true from there.
所以我要去测试
So I'm going to test,
if (isItNaN(x) &&
if (isItNaN(x) &amp;&amp;
isItNaN (y))。
isItNaN(y)).
如果是这样我们肯定知道回报是真的他们都是纳尼丝
And if that's the case, we definitely
know return true, cuz they're both NaNs,
这就是我们想说实话的地方
and this is the case where
we wanna tell the truth.
如果两个人都不这样的话我们真正需要做的就是
And if neither one of those too is the
case then really all we need to do is to
再等三等比
further the triple equals.
所以我们只返回 x === y;
So we simply return x === y;.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 让我们来处理这个问题。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So
let's handle this particular case up here.
如果有一个或两个我们还不确定
If one or
both of them we're not sure yet, but
我们知道其中至少有一个是负 0
we know at least one of
them is a negative 0.
那我们怎么知道是否要回归真假 ?
Then how do we know if we
should return true or not?
只有两个都是负 0的
Well, only if both of them are negative 0.
所以我们可以简单地说，返回 xNegZero & yNegZero;。
So we can simply say here
return xNegZero &amp;&amp; yNegZero;.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 所以我之前就知道的最优化的
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So the little
pre-optimization that I already knew about
我得检查两次所以我就去了
was that I was gonna need to check
it twice so I went ahead and
将其转换为变量，而不是对函数调用进行两次检查。
cashed it into a variable instead of
checking it twice with the function call.
>> Kyle Simpson: 根据您在此处看到的情况，对解决方案文件进行双重检查，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Double checking against
the solution file, as you see over here,
而我写的几乎是一样的
and I've written it almost the same.
我就用我刚写的代码
I'm gonna just take this
code that I just wrote
这里， >> 凯尔 - 辛普森:
here,
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: And
我有个小环境
I have a little environment.
这个程序叫 Run JS ，就像一个控制台来执行一些东西，
This program's called Run JS, which is
like a console that executes stuff,
这不完美但很不错
it's not perfect but it's pretty good.
所以我要把这个代码放到这儿来
So I'm gonna drop this code into here and
run it.
我们应该看到所有真实的真相
And we should see all trues and we do.